<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_title">How-To Boarding a Oki-Kisen Ferry\n(April, 2019 written)</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_1">[Booked]\n"Ferry-Oki", "Ferry-Kuniga", and "Ferry-Shirashima" can make a reservation by telephone for more than special-class2 seats and vehicle transportation. It will not be full, but keep standing for two hours at the peak of congestion. Vehicle transportation may be full.\n"Rainbow Jet" is available for phone or Internet reservations.\nMake a reservation in advance as much as possible in the "Rainbow Jet". Weekends and national holidays are full year.</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_2">[Operating status] around 6:30 a.m. on the day Ferry schedules may be changed or cancelled during high winds and high waves. There are many high-wave days in the sea of Japan in winter. Be sure to check the operation status on the official website. Especially, the Rainbow Jet has a higher rate of cancellation compared to ferries, and even if the wind is calm, it cannot be relieved. It is a common thing to cancel due to an engine failure.</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_3">[Sakaiminato-port and Shichirui-port access] up to 30 minutes before departure, if you want to put the vehicle up to 1 hour before\nDo not make a mistake because the "Sakaiminato port" and the "Shichirui port" are far away.\nBecause the parking lot of "Sakaiminato" is small, it is convenient to visit by the public transportation such as "Kitaro-train". When parking, you must get a permit at the window.\nThe parking lot of "Shichirui port" is wide, so it is near full in summer, so it is recommended to use the bus from Yonago, Matsue and Sakaiminato.\nBecause the temporary parking lot is established every year in the Bon period, let\'s look well beforehand.</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_4">[Boarding Procedure]\nFill out the boarding form and purchase the ticket at the window.\nIn the case of the vehicle transportation, the car verification is necessary at the window. Let\'s prepare beforehand.\nIf you have a reservation, we will inform you at the window.</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_5">[How to spend time waiting]\nWhen you purchase a ticket, you are free to start boarding time. It\'s nice to stroll around the area and look around the souvenir shops. It is also good to buy a drink because the throat is thirsty while sailing.</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_6">[Boarding start] 15 minutes before departure\nThe ferry\'s rooms are sleeping together in a huddle.Crowded when sitting down. A good position such as wall can be a procession in the contact passage because the early person wins.\nWhen the rooms are full, you can also sit there on the inboard aisle. Goza can be borrowed for free from sailors.\nThe rooms at Rainbow jet are seats only and all seats are free. You can see a good view from the window seat on the second floor.</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_7">[How to spend on the ship]\nYou can rent a blanket for 30 yen on the ferry. Pillows are free. If the sea conditions are calm, it is also good to go out to the deck and bathe the wind. It is recommended to sleep early on the high-wave day. Otherwise, you will spend two hours in the toilet.\nRainbow jet wearing seat-belt during sailing, so there is no place to look around on the ship, you will spend the seat until arrival.</string>
    <string name="guide_okikisen_8">Have a nice trip!</string>
</resources>
