<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_title">How-To Boarding a Inter-Islands Ferry\n(April, 2019 written)</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_1">[Booked]\nReservation is not possible.\nIt does not become full, and when there are a lot of passengers, even a "Isokaze" with a small capacity, two ships perform a scheduled operation.\nThe "Ferry-Dozen" vehicle transport may be full.</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_2">[Operating status] from the day\nFerry schedules may be changed or cancelled during high winds and high waves. When the West wind is strong, the rate of cancellation of  "to Kurii-port, Chibu village" is high.\nCheck the operation status on the website of the Tourism Association.\nIf there is a change in the ferry schedule, public announcement at "Chibu village", "Ama Town", and "Nishinoshima Town" .</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_3">[Access] up to 10 minutes before departure\nDo not make a mistake because the port of Beppu is far away from the "Ferry-Dozen" and "Isokaze" boarding point. There are many people who miss because of the mistake.\nSince the vehicle transportation is a first-come order, let\'s head ahead early in the congestion.</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_4">[Boarding Procedure]\nBuy tickets at the ticket vending machine. You can pay cash on board without buying tickets. Because there is no ticket machine and the "Kurii-port, Chibu village", it is only on-board payment.\nIn the case of the vehicle transportation, the procedure is made at the window. The length of the car will be asked. The first operation of "Ferry-Dozen" (from Hishiura port, Ama town) and the last operating(from Beppu Port, Nishinoshima town) are closed, so pay the sailors in cash. Since there is no window for the departure from the "Kurii-port, Chibu village", we only pay on board.</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_5">[How to spend time waiting]\nYou can experience the extraordinary by just looking at the sea from the quay.</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_6">[Boarding start] 3 to 10 minutes before departure\nThere is usually no boarding guide. When everyone starts on board, let\'s Ride together.\nThe seat is free. Let\'s sit where we want to be.</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_7">[How to spend on the ship]\nWhen the weather is nice, you can go out to the deck and soak up the sea breeze. Once a year, dolphins can be seen during sailing.</string>
    <string name="guide_naikousen_8">Now you can see the next island!</string>
</resources>
